(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T21:37:03.141574",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
おはよう！
Good morning!
私は今来たところ全然待ってないよ。
I just got here, I wasn't waiting at all.
むしろ今日は来てくれてありがとう！
In fact, thank you for coming today!
いい天気だね。
The weather's great, huh?
私さ、ずっと君とこうやって公園とか散歩したいと思ってたんだ。
You know, I've always wanted to take a walk in the park like this with you.
あのさ、手、繋いでもいいかな？
Hey, um... do you mind if we hold hands?
やった！繋いじゃおう。
Yay! Let's hold hands.
手を繋いでると、なんかなんかドキドキするね。
Holding hands makes my heart flutter somehow.
いよいよこれから生誕ライブか。
The birthday live is finally coming up.
緊張するな。
I'm getting nervous.
君ももちろん来てくれるよね？
Of course you're coming too, right?
ありがとう。今日のために歌とかダンスとかいっぱい練習してきたから。
Thank you. I've been practicing singing and dancing a lot for today.
絶対見てほしいと思ってたんだ。
I really wanted you to see it.
絶対見つけるね。
I'll definitely find you.
あ、あそこにベンチがあるよ。
Ah, there's a bench over there.
ちょっと座って話そう。
Let's sit down and talk for a bit.
なんかさ、一つの椅子に隣同士で座るとさ、なんかドキドキするね。
You know, sitting side by side on one bench makes my heart flutter.
かわいい。
So cute.
ところで、お昼ご飯食べた？
By the way, did you eat lunch?
そっか、まだ食べてないんだ。
Ah, I see, you haven't eaten yet.
そうだと思って、
"I thought so, and..."
実は今日、君のために手作りの弁当を作ってきたんだ！
"Actually, I made a handmade bento for you today!"
一緒に食べよ？
"Let's eat together?"
ありがとう。
"Thank you."
じゃじゃーん！見て！これ、お弁当箱可愛いでしょう？
"Ta-da! Look! Isn't this bento box cute?"
中身、何入ってると思う？
"What do you think is inside?"
卵焼き？コロッケ？ハンバーグ？
"Tamagoyaki? Croquette? Hamburg steak?"
うんうん。なるほど？
"Mm-hm. I see."
正解は……こちらでしたー！じゃーん！
"The correct answer is... this! Ta-da!"
わあ！美味しそう！
"Wow! It looks delicious!"
どうかな？あずきの手作りお弁当、
"How is it? Azki's handmade bento,"
題して「あなたのハートを狙い撃さん！弁当」だよ！
"titled 'Targeting Your Heart! Bento'!"
君の好きな卵焼きもちゃんと入ってます。正解だよ！
"Your favorite tamagoyaki is in here too. You got it right!"
それじゃあ、何から食べる？
"Well then, what will you eat first?"
ソーセージ？トマト？卵焼き？
"Sausage? Tomato? Tamagoyaki?"
うんうん。やっぱり大好物の卵焼きからか！本当好きだよね！
"Mm-hm. Starting with your favorite tamagoyaki, huh! You really love it!"
じゃあさ、
"Well then,"
「あーん」してあげよっか。
"shall I feed you 'ah-n'?"
もう、うなずきすぎだよ！可愛いな。
"Geez, you're nodding too much! So cute."
はい、じゃあ、あーん。
"Here, then, say 'ah-n'."
どう？美味しい？
"How is it? Is it delicious?"
ありがとう！嬉しい！
"Thank you! I'm so happy!"
はい、じゃあもう一口。あーん。
"Okay, then one more bite. Say 'ah-n'."
美味しそうに食べるね！作った甲斐があった！美味しそうに食べてる君もあずきは好きだよ！
"You eat with such gusto! It was worth making! Azki loves seeing you eat deliciously too!"
食べてる君の姿見てたらあずきも元気出た！今日の生誕ライブも頑張れそうだよ！
"Seeing you eat gave me energy too! I feel like I can do my best in today's birthday live!"
それじゃあ、そろそろリハーサルの時間だから行ってくるね！
"Well then, it's almost time for rehearsal, so I'm off!"
絶対見つけるからね！ライブが終わったらまた待ち合わせね！
"I'll definitely find you! Let's meet up again after the live!"
せーの！
Ready, go!
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's a no-no,
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
And that's still not enough, hey,
心は進化するよ もっと もっと
My heart is evolving more and more!
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words would make our relationship vanish,
言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた 恐れてた
I thought—I was afraid—that we should just erase words.
だけど あれ？ なんか違うかも
But huh? Maybe something's different...
千里の道も一歩から！
Every long journey begins with a single step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a determination as hard as stone,
ちりも積もればやまとでしこ？ 「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で！
Dust builds up to make a Yamato nadeshiko? Skipping the 'shi'? No, with all my might!
ふわふわり ふわふわる あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Fluffily, fluffily floating, just you calling my name
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
makes me float into the sky.
ふわふわる ふわふわり あなたが笑っている
Fluffily, fluffily floating, just you smiling
それだけで 笑顔になる
makes me smile too.
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's just a twist of fate,
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I'm so happy that we were able to meet!
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's a no-no,
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
And that's still not enough, hey,
心は進化するよ もっと もっと
My heart is evolving more and more!
そう そんなんじゃいやだ ねぇ そんなんじゃまだ
Yup, that's a no-go, hey, that's still too early,
私のこと見ててね ずっと ずっと
Don't take your eyes off me, never and ever!
私の中のあなたほど あなたの中の私の存在は
The more of you in me, and that my existence in you,
まだまだ大きくないことも わかってるけれど
I know that I'm not as big as you,
今この同じ瞬間 共有してる実感
but in this same moment, I feel that we share it.
ちりも積もればやまとでしこ！ 略して？ちりもつもやまとでこ！
If all the dust settles, yamato nadeshiko! For short? If the dust settles, it's yamato nadeshiko!
くらくるり くらくるる あなたを見上げたら
Swooningly, swoonity, when I look at you,
それだけで まぶしすぎて
just that will make me daze to your radiance.
くらくるる くらくるり
Swoonity, swooningly...
あなたを想っている
Thinking of you,
それだけでとけてしまう
just that makes me melt away.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God.
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a twist of fate,
めぐり逢えたことが
the fact that we met
しあわせなの
makes me so happy.
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
The season of love is greedy circulation.
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
Feelings of love are greedy circulation.
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
Eyes in love are greedy circulation.
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
Maidens in love are greedy circulation.
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffy and light, floating away,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
when you call my name, I float up to the sky.
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Floating and light, fluffy and soft,
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
when you smile, it puts a smile on my face.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God.
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a twist of fate,
めぐり逢えたことが
the fact that we met
しあわせなの
makes me so happy.
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good,
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
hey, that's still not enough.
心は進化するよ もっと もっと
My heart is evolving more and more.
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't want it like that,
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
hey, that's still not enough.
私のこと 見ててね ずっと ずっと
Keep looking at me forever and ever.
ひとくち、ちょうだい？
A bite, please?
ねぇ それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
恋人みたいなことしてみたいの
I want to try doing things like lovers do.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
ねぇ それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...is what I couldn't say on today's date.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
目が合うだけで頬が緩む
Just locking eyes makes my cheeks soften,
目尻のしわくしゃ たまらないの
and crinkles at the corners of my eyes are irresistible.
週末 弾けた恋模様
A weekend of sparkling romantic patterns—
心が微熱どころではない
my heart is running a fever beyond just a mild one.
ときめきの夢に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by a dreamy thrill,
いっそこのまま死んでもいい…?!
I wouldn't mind even dying right now...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, because I love you.
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stop right here.
幸せを噛み締めたいな ずっと
I want to savor this happiness forever.
このまま覚めないで
Don't let this dream wake up,
あともう一口だけ
just one more bite.
許されるならば夢を見せて
If I'm allowed, show me a dream.
ねぇ それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
間接キスなんてもう気にしないよ
I don't care about indirect kisses anymore.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
ねぇ それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
……あなたが好きすぎて言い出せないよ
...I love you too much to say it out loud.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
もうそろそろ気持ちが爆発しそうだよ
My feelings are about to explode soon,
抱きしめてみたいよ
I want to try hugging you.
でも引かれたら立ち直れないし…
But if you pulled away, I couldn't recover...
臆病なの、変わらないや
I'm still just as cowardly as ever.
目が合うだけで心臓が飛ぶ
Just locking eyes makes my heart leap,
せめて手だけは繋ぎたいの
at least I want to hold hands.
週末 弾けた恋模様
A weekend of sparkling romantic patterns—
心が微熱どころではない
my heart is running a fever beyond just a mild one.
もう一度 夢に酔いしれて
Once more, intoxicated by a dream,
連れ出して！
take me away!
いっそこのまま死んでもいい…?!
I wouldn't mind even dying right now...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, because I love you.
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stop right here.
幸せを噛み締めたいな ずっと
I want to savor this happiness forever.
このまま覚めないで
Don't let this dream wake up,
あともう一口だけ
just one more bite.
許されるならば夢を見せて
If I'm allowed, show me a dream.
日が暮れるまで傍に居て
Stay by my side until the sun sets.
初キスはもう少し後で
Save our first kiss for a little later.
束縛は強めでOK？
Is strong confinement/clinginess okay?
受け止めて 受け止めて
Accept me, accept me.
何も言わずに手を引いて
Take my hand without saying a word,
そのまま遠くへ連れてって どこまでも どこまでも
and take me far away, on and on, wherever it goes.
ねぇ それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that.
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to taste one bite.
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...is what I couldn't say on today's date.
……とは言い出せなかった 今日のデート
...What I couldn't bring myself to say was today's date.
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I just want a bite.
今、私は恋してるの！
Right now, I'm in love!
はーい！ということでみんな、こんこんこんこんこんあずきー！
Hi! So everyone, kon-kon-kon-kon-kon-Azukee!
右手にマイク、左手にチーズ、あなたのハートを狙い撃さん！AZKiでーす！
Mic in my right hand, cheese in my left, shooting straight for your heart! I'm AZKi!
ということで、本日はAZKi 7thバースデーライブ「Sweet Pop Story」にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
So, thank you very much for coming to AZKi's 7th Birthday Live "Sweet Pop Story" today!
わーい！わいわいわいわい！始まった、始まった！
Yay! Yay yay yay yay! It started, it started!
え、なんと活動を始めて、7回目の誕生日を迎えることができましたー！
Um, somehow, having started activities, I was able to celebrate my 7th birthday!
本当に本当にいつも応援してくれる開拓者のみんなのおかげで、今日の日が、この日があると、思っています。いつもありがとう！
Really, really, thanks to all the pioneers who always support me, I believe today and this day exist. Thank you always!
ということで、なんとね、もう今日は冒頭から！
So, you know, today right from the very beginning!
新衣装をお披露目でございます！
We are revealing our new outfit!
どうかな？どうかな？どうかな？
How is it? How is it? How is it?
どう？どう？どう？どう？どう？どう？どう？
How? How? How? How? How? How? How?
はい、今回の、え、新衣装のテーマはですね、え、ゆるふわ私服衣装となっておりまーす！
Yes, the theme for this new outfit is... um, a loose and fluffy casual wear style!
かわいいでしょ？かわいいでしょ？はい！
Isn't it cute? Isn't it cute? Yes!
ということでね、こういうね、なんかその私服っぽくてかわいい衣装がいいなって、ほしいなって思っていたので今回お仕立てしていただきましたー！
So, you know, I wanted a casual, cute outfit like this, so this time I had it specially made!
そしてね、今日のこのライブステージも、この衣装に合せて！
And, today's live stage as well, matched with this outfit!
なんとなんと、見てください皆さん！ちょっとお部屋っぽく、ちょっとね、デートもできそうなステージになっておりまーす！
Look at that, everyone! It's like a room, a stage where we could even go on a date!
ね、このね、新衣装にぴったりのステージになってまっす！
Right, it's a stage that fits this new outfit perfectly!
はい、ということで今日はね、
Yes, so today,
あの、この配信のハッシュタグ、右上ここ！これこれこれこれこれこれこれ！「AZKi生誕ライブ2025」で、
um, the hashtag for this stream, top right here! This this this this this! "#AZKiBirthdayLive2025",
たくさんたくさんポストしてください！
please post a lot, a lot!
スクショとか感想とか、全部全部AZKiもチェックしますんで！かわいいAZKiを！
Screenshots, impressions, AZKi will check all of them! A cute AZKi!
スクショするんだ！よろしくね！お願いしまーす！
Take screenshots! Treat me well! Please!
え、そしてそして、今日はですね、新衣装のお披露目だけでなく、重大発表もありますので、ぜひ最後まで見てください！よろしくねー！
And and, today, not only the new outfit reveal, but there are also major announcements, so please watch till the end! Please!
はい、ということでね、さっそくライブが始まったわけなんですが、ちょっと今回は「Sweet Pop Story」ということで、
Yes, so the live has just started, but this time it's "Sweet Pop Story",
ま、物語風にね、ちょっとデートなんかして、みちゃったり！
so, sort of like a story, going on a date or something!
はい。してね、今日のライブ楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！で、1曲目は「恋愛サーキュレーション」、そして、え、2曲目は「ヒトクチ、チョーダイ？」っていうね、オリジナル曲でございましたー！
Yeah. And I hope you enjoy today's live! The 1st song was "Renai Circulation", and the 2nd was our original song "Hitokuchi, Choudai!"
どうだったかな？どうだった？かわいかった？
How was it? How was it? Was it cute?
ということで、ここからなんとみんなお待ちかねのゲストブロックになります！
So, from here on, it will be the guest block everyone's been waiting for!
え、大好きなあのメンバーと可愛い曲を歌っちゃいますので、ぜひぜひ楽しんでいただけたらと思います！
We'll be singing a cute song with that member I love so much, so I hope you'll enjoy it!
それじゃいくよー！どうぞー！
Then let's go! Here we go!
浮つく甘い街の喧騒
Due to the hustle and bustle of a sweet, floating city,
故に感情線は渋滞
the emotional lines are congested.
「僕に関係ない」とか言って
Saying "It has nothing to do with me,"
心模様 白く染まって
my state of mind is dyed white.
だけどどうやったって釣り合わない
But no matter what, we don't match.
いたずらに笑う横顔に乾杯
Cheers to that mischievously smiling profile.
すいも甘いもわからないの
I don't know what's sour or sweet,
きっと君の前では迷子
surely getting lost in front of you.
溶かしてはランデブー
A rendezvous after melting,
プラトニックになってく
becoming platonic.
ほろ苦い期待 張り裂けてしまいそう
Bittersweet expectations are about to burst.
だから
So—
夢惑う
Confused in a dream...
想いならば
If it's these feelings...
聞かせて
Let me hear
その声を
that voice of yours.
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I get dyed in your colors, dyed in your colors,
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Play with my heart, don't look anywhere else.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking about it, keep thinking about it.
桃色の心予報
A pink-colored heart forecast.
今混ざってしまえば 混ざってしまえば
Now if we get mixed together, if we get mixed together,
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you as our loving gazes combine,
ロマンスは止まらない
romance won't stop.
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神さまどうか今日は味方して
Oh God, please take my side today!
おかしな君は笑って
You laugh so playfully,
逆さま世界が顔出して
and the upside-down world reveals itself.
夢ならまだ醒めないで
If it's a dream, don't wake me up yet.
心模様 赤に染まってく
My heart's mood dyes redder and redder.
冷静沈着では
With a calm and composed attitude,
どう頑張ったってない
no matter how hard I try, it's no use.
大体 視界に居ない ちょっとlateなスターライナイト
You're mostly out of sight, a little late starry night.
最低な昨日にさえ さよなら言いたいよな
I want to even say goodbye to yesterday at its worst.
甘いおまじないかけられてしまいそう
I feel like I'm about to be put under a sweet spell.
だから この夜を越えてゆけ 響かせて
So, cross over this night and let it resonate!
その想いを
That feeling,
君に染まってしまえば
if I get dyed in your colors,
君だけ想っていたいな
I want to think only of you.
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I get dyed in your colors, dyed in your colors,
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Play with my heart, don't look anywhere else.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking about it, keep thinking about it.
桃色の心予報
A pink-colored heart forecast.
今伝えてしまえば 伝えてしまえば
Now if I convey it all, if I convey it all,
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you as our loving gazes combine,
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神さまどうか今日は味方して
Oh God, please take my side today!
『スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！』
"Fall in love with me! Definitely fall in love with me!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating you together with me!
ハツコイ♡パティシエール
[Title: Hatsukoi♡Patissier]
朝からビターなキモチ
Bitter feelings right from the morning,
だって知らない表情で笑った
because you smiled with an expression I didn't know.
ちょっと髪に触れたりしちゃって
You even touched my hair a little bit,
なんでハナの下伸ばしてんの!?
so why are you stretching out the space under your nose?!
どんどん膨れてくジェラシー
My jealousy keeps swelling up more and more,
スフレみたいに甘くないよ
not as sweet as a soufflé!
胸いっぱいに溢れちゃって
Overflowing to the brim of my chest,
ダメダメ！気付かれちゃうよ！
no, no! You'll notice it!
バレないように…でも気付いて！フクサツな乙女心
So they won't find out... but please notice! A complicated maiden's heart.
『スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！』
"Fall in love with me! Definitely fall in love with me!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating you together with me!
恋心 ちょっとキャラメリゼ
My feelings of love are slightly caramelized;
焦がしたらきっとスキにさせるから！
if I scorch them, I'll definitely make you fall in love!
今日は朝からちょっとラッキー
Today started off a bit lucky since morning—
あくびこらえた変顔見ちゃった
I saw your funny face trying to hold back a yawn!
肩叩きながら「おはよ」なんて言えたらもっと…あぁ！もう！イケナイ！
If I could tap your shoulder and say "Good morning", more... Ah! Jeez! No way!
ふぅ…ちょっと落ち着いて？
Whew... calm down a little, okay?
モンテしすぎて零れちゃうよ
Whip it too much and it'll overflow!
「なにしてんの？」ってほっぺツンツン
"What are you doing?" poking your cheeks.
いきなりまさかの不意打ち禁止～!!
A sudden, unexpected surprise attack is forbidden~!
メレンゲハート 耳までキュイール アツいのは私だけ？
Meringue heart, heating up all the way to my ears, am I the only one getting hot?
スキすぎる！あぁ…スキすぎる！
Loving you too much! Ah... loving you too much!
ココロから スペシャリテのアイラブユー
From the bottom of my heart, a spécialité "I love you"!
恋心 もっとタブラージュ
My feelings of love, more and more table-u-ge...
溶けたならハート型にグラッセしよ
If they melt, let's glaze them into heart shapes!
アナタだけに 教えてあげる
I'll teach only you...
このキモチのヒミツ
the secret of these feelings.
『ダイスキだよ！』
"I love you!"
『スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！』
"Fall in love with me! Definitely fall in love with me!"
おまじない
A magic spell...
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A spell, decorating you together...
このキモチ ずっとアラカルト
This feeling is always à la carte.
おすそわけ ココロごとデコレーション
Sharing it, decorating with all my heart...
恋心 いっぱいプレゼント
A full presentation of love in my heart.
届いたら 私ごと召し上がれ♪
When it reaches you, please eat me up too!
Lalala...
なーににしようか 練習中
What should I do? In the middle of practice,
しれっとこそっと 準備進行
Quietly and secretly, preparations are underway,
心境 緊張で焦る
I'm nervous and flustered about my state of mind.
言わんけどつよつよアリでしょ?
I won't say it, but being super strong is fine, right?
元気配るからまっちょって
I'll share my energy, so wait for me,
そうやって 成長する子です
I'm a child who grows by doing that.
いいかな
Is that okay?
ゆるポンでOK?
Are you okay with 'Yuru-pon'?
いちにーさん
One, two, three,
テンパっちゃってOK?
Are you okay even if I panic?
始めちゃおう
Let's start!
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want you to praise me, I want you to praise me,
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll do my best with 20% more effort!
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me,
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows when praised endlessly.
なぁーんにも出てこない
Nothing at all comes to mind,
頭ん中真っ白だ
My head is completely blank,
さっぱりだ うんうん あれ?
Completely blank, yeah yeah, huh?
まいっか
Oh well!
凸凹な情勢 提供中
Providing an uneven situation,
ぽかんとして何しちょんの
Staring blankly, what are you doing?
こんなが通常のわたし
This is the usual me.
いいでしょ
Isn't that fine?
それではOK?
Then, is that OK?
いちにーさん
One, two, three,
落ち着きOK?
Is being calm OK?
始めちゃおう
Let's start!
どうしたらいいの? どうしたらいいの?
What should I do? What should I do?
どうすればみんなハッピで笑顔バッチリ
How can I make everyone happy and smiling perfectly?
こちらへどうぞ こちらへどうぞ
Come here, please, come here, please,
押さず慌てず並んで合図です
Without pushing, without panicking, line up, it's the signal!
聞こえてる?
Can you hear me?
楽しんでる?
Are you enjoying it?
こっちだよ
It's this way!
少し眠いな 少し眠いな
I'm a little sleepy, I'm a little sleepy,
また明日食べて寝て今は成長期
Let's eat and sleep again tomorrow, now is my growing period.
夢を見たいな 夢を見たいな
I want to dream, I want to dream,
どうぞくれぐれもあの.. 今後も
Please, take good care of me, now and in the future too.
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want you to praise me, I want you to praise me,
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll do my best with 20% more effort!
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me,
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows when praised endlessly.
またね
See you later!
sweet night, sweet time...
そっと陽の沈む茜の空
Softly the sun sets in the crimson sky,
やっと目覚めたきみに挨拶
Finally saying hello to you who just woke up.
えっと明日は休みだから
Well, tomorrow is a holiday, so
一晩中きみといっしょに
All night long together with you!
sweet night, sweet time...
眠くないよ 眠くないの
I'm not sleepy, I'm not sleepy.
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
まだまだ遊びたい
I still want to play.
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
話したいよ 話し足りないの
I want to talk, I haven't talked enough.
夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Since it's not satisfying in a dream,
今夜は 寝なーい 眠らない
Tonight... I won't sleep, I won't sleep.
きみとリズム合わせ
Matching rhythms with you.
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
Enjoying the reversal of day and night.
今だけ 寝なーい 眠らない
Just for now... I won't sleep, I won't sleep.
星の中散歩して
Taking a walk among the stars,
夜がどうか明けないように
Hoping the night never ends.
いつまでも いつまでも
Forever and ever...
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
きっと話すのも笑うのも
Surely, both talking and laughing
もっと誰かとつながるため
are to connect more with someone.
ちょっと俯いたきみへ向けて
Turning toward you, who are slightly looking down,
一晩中 歌ってもいい
it's okay to sing all night long.
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
眠らないよ 眠らないの
I'm not sleepy, I'm not sleepy.
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
夜ごと遊びたい
I want to play every night.
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
喋りたいよ 喋り足りないの
I want to talk, I haven't talked enough.
sweet night, sweet time…
sweet night, sweet time...
きみと朝まで
Until the morning with you.
月も知らない
That even the moon doesn't know,
ナイショ話を
secrets...
パジャマのままで
In my pajamas,
お願い
please.
夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Since it's not satisfying in a dream,
もう少し…
just a little longer...
寝なーい 眠らない
I won't sleep, I won't sleep.
きみとリズム合わせ
Matching rhythms with you.
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
Enjoying the reversal of day and night.
今だけ 寝なーい 眠らない
Just for now... I won't sleep, I won't sleep.
白む空見送って
Watching off the whitening sky,
夜を越えよう また明日もここで会おう
Let's go beyond the night, let's meet here tomorrow too.
good night, good time…
good night, good time...
また明日
See you tomorrow.
good night, good time…
good night, good time...
と言うわけでゲストブロックをお送りしました！
And so, we brought you the guest block!
どうだったかなどうだったかな？
How was it, how was it?
はい、というわけでゲストパートなんですが、
Yes, so as for the guest part,
ここまでを振り返ると、いろはちゃんと、
looking back so far, with Iroha-chan
心予報をお届けしました！
and "Kokoro Yopo," we delivered!
なんとね、いろはちゃんの新衣装を3Dでね、
And amazingly, in Iroha-chan's new 3D outfit,
一緒にこれはAZ色決定？AZ色てぇてぇをしたいと思って、
we wanted to do "AZ Color Teetee" together,
一緒にね歌ってみたを出した心予報を
so we released a singing cover of "Kokoro Yopo"
踊って一緒にAZ色てぇてぇしました。どうだった？
and danced together. How was it?
そして、次はラミィちゃんとの初恋パティスリー
And next, with Lamy-chan, "First Love Patisserie,"
というラミィちゃんのオリ曲をね、
Lamy-chan's original song,
このライブのテーマに絶対合うと思って歌わせていただきました！
I thought it fit the live theme so I sang it!
そして、団長と褒めの日！
And, Danchou and Homenobi!
ずっとずっとAZと一緒に褒めの日を歌うのが夢だったんで、
It's been my dream forever to sing Homenobi with AZ,
このライブで実現するぞと思って、褒めの日で成長していきたいと甘えます！
so I made it happen at this live to grow through Homenobi!
そしてわためと一緒に、わためのオリジナル曲を歌わせていただきました！
And together with Watame, we sang her original song!
これも今回のコンセプトにめちゃくちゃ合うわと思って選曲しました！どうだったかな？
I chose it because it fits the concept so well! How was it?
ホロメンのオリ曲歌ったりできるの本当にライブならではという感じで、
Being able to sing Holomen's original songs feels so unique to a live,
お届けしましたが、まだまだゲストパート続きますんで、
but the guest part still continues,
セトリストのAZKiさんにもご注目ください！
so please also pay attention to AZKi-san's setlist!
ということで、まだまだゲストパート行くぞー！
With that said, we're still going with the guest part!
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wagging tails, it's a scout!
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering more cute girls!
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
Once we gather, we're unbeatable!
文化祭が始まる
The school festival begins!
最大規模で行きたいの
We want it on a grand scale!
君も参加してよね
You should join in too!
ネットチケット無制限
Unlimited online tickets!
校長先生もビックリ
Even the principal is surprised!
キャストたんない大慌て
Not enough cast members, total panic!
ワンワン泣いちゃううううう
Crying like a puppy, waaaah!
本番間近 胃はキリキリ
The big day is near, my stomach hurts!
運営の予算はギリギリ
Management's budget is razor-thin!
すねちゃうぞ
I'll pout,
泣いちゃうぞ
I'll cry!
テレフォンナンバー pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number, pi pi pi pi pi
「イケてる子を用意して」
"Bring me some cool kids"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer!
可愛い子チェックスカウター！
Cute girl check scouter!
超超超 超超超 美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
Super super super gorgeous girl get☆
美少女捕まえた☆
Caught a gorgeous girl☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to ever die,
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Give me a flashy virtual funeral!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how serious I want to be!
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wagging tails, it's a scout!
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering more cute girls!
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
Once we gather, we're unbeatable!
あー無駄足三昧しんどいお
Ugh, endless wasted steps, so exhausting~
どうしようもない焦燥感
A helpless sense of impatience
タイムリミットあとちょっと！？
Time limit is just a bit away!?
ここらでもいっちょ！
Let's give it one more try here!
美味しいころね食べたら
If you eat delicious Korone,
犬に金棒最強よ！
Like giving a dog a club, we're unstoppable!
東西南北 駆け回り
Running around from east to west, north to south,
まだ見ぬあの子 探し出せ！
Find that yet-unseen girl!
ワンワン鳴いちゃう わおん
Barking like a puppy, waon,
わおーん！
waon!
呼ばれたらどこでも駆けつけます！
If called, I'll rush anywhere!
いい子がいたら、教えてね
If there's a good girl, let me know!
拗ねちゃうぞ
I'll pout,
甘えちゃうぞ
I'll act spoiled!
テレフォンナンバー pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number, pi pi pi pi pi
「イケてる子が見つかった？」
"Did you find a cool kid?"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer!
可愛い子チェックスカウター！
Cute girl check scouter!
超超超 超超超 美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
Super super super gorgeous girl get☆
美少女捕まえた☆
Caught a gorgeous girl☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to ever die,
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Give me a flashy virtual funeral!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how serious I want to be!
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wagging tails, it's a scout!
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering more cute girls!
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
Once we gather, we're unbeatable!
実戦対面は問いません
Direct meetings don't matter
「私、君を待ってるよ」ふっ♪
"I'll be waiting for you." Heh♪
うー、あー、もー、はいっ！
Oo, ah, mo, hei!
やだやだミスってらんない、ね？
No way, I can't mess up, right?
真っ赤なハート差し出して…そんなのやっぱ妄想じゃん
Offering a red heart... that's just a delusion
そっちはどう思ってるの？言いかけて仕舞う無理みたい
What do you think? I start to say it and stop, seems impossible
こんなんじゃ…ってわかってるんだ思うほどにハマっていくんだ
I know it's like this... the more I think, the deeper I fall
頑張りたいあたしに期待 ぎゅーだってしたいかも…かもん
Expectations for me who wants to try, maybe I even want a hug... c'mon
ちょっと変われていますか？
Have I changed a bit?
足りないことばっかだけど
Even though I'm still lacking everywhere
ポンでコツでドジじゃないあたしだったら きみはだめだよね？
If I wasn't a clumsy, scatterbrained me, you wouldn't want me, right?
ねえもうやだやだミスってらんない
Hey, no way, no way, I can't mess up
もうやだやだ踊ってベイビーダンス
No way, no way, dance, baby dance
あたしはまだ諦めない でもでも全然だめかも
I still won't give up, but maybe it's totally no good
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
'Cause it's baby dance, I can't do it right
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
'Cause it's baby dance, I can't convey it
もっと可愛くなりたいのにどうしたらいいとかわかんないし
Even though I want to be cuter, I don't know what to do
やだやだミスってらんない、ね？
No way, I can't mess up, right?
あーやっちまったこんなはずじゃ
Ah, I messed up, this wasn't supposed to happen
どうしてどうしてわかっているのに
Why, why, even though I understand,
見せたくないとこ透けちゃって 無理無理
The parts I don't want to show peek through, no way
でも期待はしたいな いいですか？
But I still want to have expectations, is that alright?
ポンもコツもドジも全部あたしなんだよ ちゃんと見ていてほしい
Clumsy and foolish, all of it is me, I want you to watch
ねえもうやだやだぐずって後悔
Hey, no way, no way, whining and regretting
もうやだやだ回ってベイビーダンス
No way, no way, spinning around, baby dance
だめなあたし塗り替えたい でもでも全然だめかも
I want to repaint my useless self, but maybe it's no good
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
'Cause it's baby dance, I can't do it right
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
'Cause it's baby dance, I can't convey it
もっと可愛くなりたいのにどうしたらいいとかわかんないし
Even though I want to be cuter, I don't know what to do
まだまだいけるかな
Can I still keep going?
うー、あー、もー、はい
Oo, ah, mo, hai
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No, no, I can't slip up, okay?
まだまだ 言えるかな
Can I still say it?
まだまだ できるかな
Can I still do it?
まだまだ… うぅ…
Still... ugh...
ポンでコツでドジでダメで足りないことばっかだって
Clumsy, foolish, hopeless, and full of flaws,
きっとやめないんだ
I'll surely never stop.
ポンでコツでドジでダメで足りないことばっかだって
Clumsy, foolish, hopeless, and full of flaws,
見ていてほしい
I want you to watch me.
ういえーい！
Wahoo!
ねぇもうやだやだ ミスってらんない
Hey, no more, no more, I can't slip up.
もうやだやだ 踊って ベイビーダンス
No more, no more, dance to the baby dance.
あたしはまだ諦めない ほらほら 全然だめじゃない
I still won't give up, look, I'm not useless at all!
だって ベイビーダンス うまくできるから
Because it's the baby dance, I can do it well.
だって ベイビーダンス 伝えられるから
Because it's the baby dance, I can convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいから どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
I want to be cuter, so no matter when, I can work hard.
だって ベイビーダンス きみに届くまで
Because it's the baby dance, until it reaches you,
だって ベイビーダンス きみに会えるまで
Because it's the baby dance, until I can meet you,
もっと可愛くなりたいから どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
I want to be cuter, so no matter when, I can work hard.
やだやだ ミスってらんないね？
No, no, I can't slip up, right?
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Surprise
Service
We are スティーレ！！
We are Stile!!
ほなぺてぃーと♡S
Bon Appétit ♡ S
さあ扉を開けて
Now, open the door
未知なるパラダイス 体験しよう
And let's experience an unknown paradise.
おいで おいでYOU
Come on, come on, YOU!
そうキミを待つのは 不思議なオアシス
Yes, waiting for you is a mysterious oasis.
ほっこり日常に ちっぽりSpice
A cozy daily life with a tiny pinch of spice.
ぐーるんぐーるん かきまぜちゃうんだ
Spinning and spinning, let's stir it all up.
ぐるんぐるん 当店自慢のフレーバー
Spinning, spinning, our store's proud flavor.
サービスサービス ご褒美タイム
Service, service, reward time!
おもてなし ココロこめて
Hospitality, put your heart into it.
Welcome to...
わーい！
Yay!
わたし達と一緒に めくるめくワンダーデイズリー
Together with us, in a dazzling wonder daysly
愛情マシマシ 煩悩ナデナデ
Affection extra, petting away worldly desires,
誠心誠意 つとめます
With sincere dedication, we will serve.
いえーす！
Yes!
キミの元気チャージにひと役かえるかな
Can we play a part in charging up your energy?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも 意外と悪くないでしょ？
Doesn't this kind of vibe, or that kind of vibe, seem surprisingly not bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい キみにきゅんきゅんきゅん ぱいんぱいんぱいん
Buono Buono, I want to blend it, making you go doki-doki-doki, pine-pine-pine!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend it.
お口にあいますか？
Does it suit your palate?
お口にあうといいな♪
I hope it suits your taste♪
ほなぺてぃーと… 千客万来らーい！
Bon Appétit... A flood of customers, welcome!
ちょっと、なんか、不本意ながらも
Though somewhat, like, against our better judgment,
いつだって需要は斜め上
Demand is always way off the charts.
そんじゃいっか ホントのわたしは シークレットモードで営業スイッチオン
Oh well, my true self turns on the business switch in secret mode.
ぐるんぐるん かきませもっと
Spinning, spinning, stir it even more.
ぐるんぐるん キミ仕様のフレーバー
Spinning, spinning, a flavor tailored just for you.
サービスサービス 極上タイム
Service, service, supreme time.
癒しとは かくあるべき
This is how healing ought to be.
Welcome to...
わたし達のお店に 本日もようこそ
Welcome once again to our shop today.
おかえり待ってた リピートうれしいな
We were waiting for your return, happy for a repeat customer.
店員一同歓迎
All staff welcome you.
いえーす！キミのお疲れ様にピッタリのレシピで
Yes! With a recipe perfectly tailored to your fatigue,
こーゆーのどうかな あーゆーのありかな よろこんでもらえてるかな
How about this kind of thing, or is that kind okay? I wonder if you're pleased.
Smile・Sweet・Sister
Smile, Sweet, Sister
Sadistic・Surprise・Service
Sadistic, Surprise, Service
We are スティーレ！！
We are Stile!!
さあ扉を開けて 愉快なパラダイス
Now, open the door to a cheerful paradise,
怖がらずにおいで、おいで
Come on without fear, come on.
そう、いつも通りの毎日に イロドリとアソビゴコロ 召し上がれ
Yes, to your usual daily life, enjoy some color and playfulness.
ブレンド・S
Blend S
Welcome to...
わたし達と一緒に めくるめくワンダーデイズリー
Together with us, in a dazzling wonder daysly
愛情マシマシ 煩悩ナデナデ
Affection extra, petting away worldly desires,
誠心誠意 つとめます
With sincere dedication, we will serve.
いえーす！
Yes!
キミの元気チャージにひと役かえるかな
Can we play a part in charging up your energy?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも 意外と悪くないでしょ？
Doesn't this kind of vibe, or that kind of vibe, seem surprisingly not bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい キみにきゅんきゅんきゅん ぱいんぱいんぱいん
Buono Buono, I want to blend it, making you go doki-doki-doki, pine-pine-pine!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend it!
お口にあいますか？
Does it suit your taste?
お好み聞かせてね
Tell me your preferences, okay?
お口にあうといいな
I hope it suits your taste.
というわけで、引き続きゲストブロックをお送りしましたー！
So, we've continued bringing you the guest block!
どうだったかな？どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい、ということで、このあとはですね、重大発表もございますので、ぜひ最後まで見てねー！
Yes, so after this, we have some major announcements, so please be sure to watch until the end!
はい、そんなゲストブロックの後半なんですが、え、ころさんと可愛いこチェックで尻尾ふりふりしましたー！
Yes, and for the second half of that guest block, um, I wagged my tail with Korosan in the "kawaii ko check"!
え、そして、みこちと、え、ベビーダンスをお送りしましたね。一緒にさ、制服衣装でね、年少味あったんじゃないかなって思います。
And, we brought you Baby Dance with Mikochi. Wearing school uniforms together, I think it gave off a cute, junior vibe!
そしてそして、ふうまっこと、え、ぼなぺてぃーと♡Sをお届けしました！今日もふうまっことね、一緒にね、こうやって3Dライブしたいなって思ってたので、
And then, we delivered "Bon Appétit ♡ S" with Fumakko! I've been wishing to do a 3D live together with Fumakko like this today, so
もう念願、念願かなって、あずきのね、やりたいことを全部全部詰め込んだゲストパートでございましたー！
My long-cherished wish came true, it was a guest part packed with everything AZKi wanted to do!
はい、ということで、まぁ重大発表もあるんですけど、
Yes, so, there are major announcements too, but
その前にみなさん、あの知らせがございます！あずき誕生日記念2025グッズ販売告知！こちらをご覧くださいー！
Before that, everyone, I have an announcement! AZKi Birthday Commemoration 2025 Goods Sales Notice! Please take a look at this!
うわー！今回もな、な、なんと、もりだくさんでございます！
Woah! This time too, my, oh my, it's so jam-packed!
え、今回イラストはD福先生に書いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
Um, this time the illustration was drawn by D-Fuku-sensei! Thank you very much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう！まずは、こちら！
Now let's look at the details! First is this!
だだだだ、抱き枕カバー！
Da-da-da-da, Dakimakura cover!
と言うことで今回のゆるふわな、え、私服の衣装で寝転がっているあずきの抱き枕カバーが出ます！うわー！まさかグッズになるとは思いませんでしたが、ぜひチェックしてください！
So, a dakimakura cover of AZKi lying down in this loose, fluffy casual outfit is coming out! Woah! I never thought it would become merchandise, but please check it out!
え、続いては、こちら！
And next is this!
缶バッジセット！え、こちらねハートの形をした缶バッジとなっております！キラキラのホログラム仕様となっておりますので、いっぱい、いっぱいね、つけてほしいなと思います！
Can badge set! Um, this is a heart-shaped can badge! Since it has a sparkly hologram finish, I hope you'll attach lots and lots of them!
続いては、こちら！
Next is this!
開拓者ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！え、ということで、ホロライブフレンズ2号のあずきとだいたいあの同じぐらいのね、ちっちゃいサイズになってますんで、一緒に、あの持ち歩いてもらえるようなサイズ感となっておりますので、一緒にね、あずぬにと、え、開拓者ぬいで、お出かけしてほしいなと思います！
Pioneer stuffed toy keychain! So, it's about the same small size as AZKi from Hololive Friends No. 2, so you can carry it around with you, so I hope you'll go out together with Azunui and the pioneer plushie!
続いては、こちら！開拓者アイマスク！まぁ今回抱き枕カバーと一緒に、もうね、安眠できるねグッズをね、え、ご用意いたしましたので、こちらもぜひ、え、寝るときに使ってほしいなと思います！
Next is this! Pioneer eye mask! Well, I prepared goods to ensure peaceful sleep together with the dakimakura cover, so I hope you'll use this when sleeping too!
そして続いては、こちら！ASMRボイス！え、ボイスタイトルは「AZKiのわがままをきいて」というね、ちょっとあずきがちょっとしたわがままを言って、君をね、デートに誘うシチュエーションとなっておりますので、今回のね、このゆるふわ私服衣装のあずきを思い浮かべて聞いてください！
And next is this! ASMR Voice! The voice title is "Listen to AZKi's Selfishness," where AZKi says a little selfish thing and invites you on a date, so please picture AZKi in this loose-fitting casual outfit and listen to it!
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！こちら！
And, there's also a full set purchase bonus! Here!
え、なんと数量限定は、あずきの直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、特典ASMRボイス、タイトルは「寝起きのAZKiと」というところで、
Um, surprisingly, the limited quantity version includes AZKi's hand-signed cheki-style bromide card and a bonus ASMR voice titled "Waking Up with AZKi"
え、こちらね、抱き枕カバーのね、なんかちょっと裏面のイラストをね、イメージしたシチュエーションとなっておりますので、こちらも一緒に楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！
inspired by the illustration on the back of the dakimakura cover, so I hope you'll enjoy it together!
続いてですね、数量限定がなくなり次第、え、白押しの複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、特典ASMRボイス、土曜の「寝起きのAZKiと」となっておりますのでよろしくお願いします！
Next, once the limited quantity runs out, there's a foil-stamped replica signed cheki-style bromide card and a bonus ASMR voice, "Waking Up with AZKi (Saturday Version)," so please look forward to it!
え、改めてフルセットはこちらとなります！じゃん！
So, again, the full set is this! Ta-da!
いやー、いっぱいね、ありますね！買うならね、やっぱね、フルセットがいいですよ！みんなよろしくね、このあと！
Man, there are so many! If you're going to buy, the full set is definitely best! Everyone, please check it out afterwards!
はい、そしてさらにタレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典といたしまして、
Yes, and as an extra full-set bonus for talent premium goods,
去年から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚つきます！カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となります！
a card usable in the Hololive Official Card Game released since last year will be included! The card applies only to those who purchased at the Hololive Production Official Shop!
特典につくのは推しをアピールできるキーカード推しホロメンカードでございます！カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページをご確認ください！同梱するカードは日本語版のみとなります！
The card included as a bonus is an oshi holomen card that lets you showcase your oshi! Please check the homepage for card details and how to play! The included card is Japanese version only!
しますので ご了承ください
Thank you for your understanding.
以上、AZKi誕生日記念2025のグッズ情報でした！
That's all for the AZKi Birthday Commemoration 2025 merch info!
みんな買ってね、ぜひよろしくお願いしますっ！
Everyone please buy it, we'd really appreciate your support!
ということで お待たせいたしました。
And so, thank you for waiting.
さらに重大発表、ございます。
Furthermore, we have a major announcement.
それではお待たせいたしました。
So without further ado...
こちらを ご覧ください！
Please take a look at this!
重大発表
[Major Announcement]
2025.11.05
Re://Birth / Re://Start
AZKi New EP
2025.11.05 ON SALE
7/1 21:00より予約受付開始
Reservations open July 1st at 21:00
はい、ということでAZKiの新しいEP『Re:Start』と『Re:Birth』が11月5日にリリースすることが決定しましたー！
Yes! So, it has been decided that AZKi's new EPs, 'Re:Start' and 'Re:Birth', will be released on November 5th!
今回は初めてとなる2作同時リリースとなっております。
This time, for the first time, two works will be released simultaneously.
このあと21時よりホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップと全国のCDショップで予約が開始されますー！
Starting at 21:00 today, reservations will open at the hololive production Official Shop and CD shops nationwide!
そして1枚目の『Re:Start』にはAZKiの新しい魅力が詰まった新曲4曲、
And the first EP, 'Re:Start', contains 4 new songs packed with AZKi's new charm,
2枚目の『Re:Birth』にはインナミュージック時代の楽曲4曲のリアレンジバージョンが収録されます。
and the second EP, 'Re:Birth', features re-arranged versions of 4 songs from her indie music era.
そして、CD限定特典としてそれぞれボーナストラックにすいちゃんと歌った『ザ・ラスト・フロンティア』が1曲ずつ収録されます。
As CD-limited bonuses, each will include a bonus track of 'The Last Frontier' sung with Suichan.
また、通常盤には限定特典としてランダムアナザージャケットが1枚ついてきます。
Additionally, the regular edition will come with one random another jacket as a limited bonus.
なんとこちらには数量限定で私の直筆サイン入りが入っているかもとのことです。
And apparently, a limited number of these will feature my handwritten signature!
各種CDショップでの購入特典はこちらです！
Here are the purchase benefits at various CD shops!
特典の絵柄は後日発表します。
The designs for the bonuses will be announced at a later date.
さらにホロライブオフィシャルショップではセットになったコンプリート盤を発売しまーす！
Furthermore, the hololive Official Shop will release a complete set version!
コンプリート盤にはここでしか手に入らないたくさんの特典もついております。
The complete edition comes with many bonuses you can only get here.
数に限りがございますのでお早めにっ！
Quantities are limited, so please order early!
そして1点、ホロライブオフィシャルショップのアルバム購入について注意点がございます。
And one important note regarding album purchases on the hololive Official Shop.
完全生産限定コンプリート盤は発売日での お届けとなりますので、EP以外のグッズとの商品は同時購入できません。
Since the complete limited edition will be delivered on the release date, it cannot be purchased simultaneously with goods other than the EP.
通常盤は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが、店頭販売日以降のお届けになる可能性があるの でこちら ご注意ください。
The regular edition can be purchased with other goods, but please note that delivery may be after the in-store release date.
詳しくは販売サイトの注意点をご確認ください。
Please check the sales site for details.
はい、そして最後に もう一つお知らせがあります。
Yes, and finally, we have one more announcement.
今回ね発表したこのニューEP『Re:Start』の中から『未来カンパネラ』という楽曲を本日24時にデジタルリリースしまーす！
From the new EP 'Re:Start' announced today, the song 'Mirai Campanella' will be digitally released tonight at 24:00!
わー、新曲だ！
Yay, a new song!
配信終了後にはミュージックビデオもプレミア公開しちゃいますということでぜひチェックしてください！
After the stream ends, the music video will also have a premiere release, so please check it out!
うわ、いっぱい情報がありましたがみんなついてこれましたか？
Whew, that was a lot of info—did everyone keep up?
はい、ということでライブも次の曲で最後になります。
Yes, so this live stream will conclude with the next song.
最後はね、AZKiの新しい曲を聴いていただきたいと思います。
For the very last song, I'd like you to listen to AZKi's new track.
それでは、聴いてください。『未来カンパネラ』。
Without further ado, please listen to 'Mirai Campanella'.
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More and more, more and more...
鏡よ 教えて 私の証は どこにあるのだろう
Mirror, tell me, where is my proof?
分からない 分からないよ
I don't know, I just don't know.
周りと比べたってさ 虚しくなるだけ
Comparing myself to those around me only leaves me empty.
あぁノイズが海鳴りのようにナミダを奪う
Ah, the noise steals my tears like the roaring sea.
切り取った風景を道しるべにしよう
Let's make this captured scenery our guiding light.
そうだ 傷ついた感情も
That's right, even these wounded emotions...
連れて行くから
I'll take you along,
そっと響くカンパネラ
softly echoing Campanella.
新しい未来を感じてる
Feeling a new future,
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ？
even if it's scary, we have to move forward, right?
遠くまで 届け
Reach far away,
この祈りよ光となれ
this prayer, become light.
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
More, more, even a little at a time, the answer called "me".
もっと もっと もっと…
More, more, more...
夜空よ 教えて
Night sky, tell me,
私の証は輝けるのかな
will my proof shine bright?
見つけたい 見つけたいよ
I want to find it, I want to find it.
誰かの決めたレールは苦しくなるだけ
Following someone else's set rail only brings pain.
ねぇノイズも力に変えるよ
Hey, I'll turn the noise into strength too.
ココロに誓う 錆びついた運命の歯車を回そう
Swearing in my heart, let's turn the rusted gears of destiny!
ほら 着飾った感情は脱ぎ捨てるから
Look, I'll strip away these dressed-up emotions,
そっと紡ぐシンフォニア 叶えたい願いを信じてる
and softly weave a symphony, believing in the wish I want to come true.
胸を張って 歌うしかないでしょ？
Standing proud, we have to sing, right?
全力で やがて希望の歌に変わる日まで
With all my might, until the day it changes into a song of hope.
もっと もっと 悩んだらでいい すべてが宝物
More, more, it's okay to worry, everything is a treasure.
いつの日かこの声を 受け取ってくれたなら
If one day you accept this voice of mine,
この言葉を君に 「もう大丈夫、一人じゃない」
I'll give these words to you: "It's alright, you're not alone."
強い想いを繋ぐよ
Connecting these strong feelings.
一歩 踏み出してみた
I tried taking a step forward,
優しく 世界は 微笑む
and the world gently smiled.
高鳴る 気持ちに 身を任せて さぁ行こう
Surrendering to my beating heart, let's go!
そっと 響く カンパネラ
Softly echoing Campanella,
新しい 未来を 感じてる
feeling a new future.
怖くたって 進む しかない でしょ？
Even if it's scary, we have to move forward, right?
遠くまで 届け
Reach far away,
この祈りよ 光となれ
this prayer, become light.
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
More, more, even a little at a time, the answer called "me".
もっと もっと もっと…
More, more, more...
ごめん、待たせた？
Sorry, kept you waiting?
ごめんね、ライブ終わったあとマネージャーさんに呼ばれちゃって
Sorry, after the live ended, my manager called me over.
もちろん、ちゃちゃっと上がったけど君と会うためにキャンセルしたんだからね。
Of course I rushed through it, because I cancelled things to meet up with you, you know.
改めて、今日はライブに来てくれてありがとう。
Again, thank you so much for coming to the live today.
アリーナ席の右の方にいたよね？
You were on the right side of the arena seats, right?
ちゃんと見つけたよ。
I definitely found you.
実は今日、花火大会なんだって。
Actually, today is a fireworks festival, apparently.
こんな都会で花火上がるの、ロマンチックだな。
Watching fireworks go off in a city like this is so romantic.
ねぇ、見て見て！今日のライブのキービジュアルだよ。
Hey, look, look! It's the key visual for today's live.
もしかしたら、ここでも流れてたのかな？
Could it have been playing here too?
ついさっきのことだからちょっと恥ずかしいよ。でも、とっても楽しかったな。
It just happened a little while ago, so I'm a bit embarrassed. But it was so much fun.
あ、雨？
Ah, rain?
どうしよう、新しい傘持ってないよ。
What should I do? I don't have a new umbrella.
あ、傘持ってきてくれたんだ！
Oh, you brought an umbrella for me!
ありがとう、かっこいいじゃん。
Thank you, that's pretty cool.
でも、傘1つしかないってことは、これって…相合い傘ってことだよね？
But, since there's only one umbrella, that means... we're sharing an umbrella, right?
私、相合い傘って初めてで、これってさ…
For me, sharing an umbrella is a first, so... this is...
あ、ドキドキするね
Ah, I'm getting so nervous...
あ、雨が止んだ
Ah, the rain has stopped.
通り雨だったのかな？
Was it just a passing shower?
なんか雨やんで、嬉しいような、悲しいような。
Somehow, with the rain stopping, I feel both happy and sad.
もっと君とイチャイチャしたかったな。
I wanted to cuddle and get closer with you more.
なんてね。
Just kidding!
雨もやんだし、雨で人通りも少なくなったしさ、
Since the rain stopped and the streets are less crowded,
グリコゲームでもしようよ。
let's play the Glico game!
ここからスタートね。
We'll start from here.
いくよ。
Here we go.
じゃんけんぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
やった！私の勝ち！
Yay! I win!
ち・よ・こ・れ・い・と
Ch-o-c-o-l-a-t-e!
ちょっと、何？にやにやして見てるの？
Hey, what? Why are you grinning and looking at me?
え？可愛いって？
Huh? I'm cute?
もう！ちょっと恥ずかしいからやめてよ。
Geez! It's kind of embarrassing, so stop it!
次いくよ。
Let's go again.
じゃんけんぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
ぐ・り・こ
G-u-r-i-c-o!
だからちょっとにやにやはやめてってば。
That's why I said stop grinning like that!
次いくよ。
Let's go next.
じゃんけんぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors, go!
ぱ・い・な・つ・ぷ・る
P-i-n-e-a-p-p-l-e!
もうじゃんけん弱すぎだよ！
You're way too weak at rock-paper-scissors!
絶対わざと負けてるでしょ！
You're definitely losing on purpose, aren't you?!
もういい加減にしてよね。
Oh, give me a break already.
え？何？こっち来てって？
Eh? What? Come over here?
どこ行くの？
Where are you going?
何々？見せたいものがある？
What, what? You have something to show me?
あのモニターを見ろって？
Look at that monitor over there?
3, 2, 1
え？えっどう言うこと？お誕生日おめでとう！
Huh? Eh, what's this? Happy birthday!
ええ！ありがとう！
Ehh! Thank you!
サプライズしてくれたんだ！
You set up a surprise for me!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
いつも一番近くで応援してくれて、本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for always supporting me right by my side!
これからもよろしくね！
I look forward to your continued support!
綺麗…
It's so beautiful...
素敵な誕生日にしてくれて、ありがとう。
Thank you for giving me such a wonderful birthday.
お礼にこの後、君だけのアンコールライブするね！
As a thank you, I'll do an encore live just for you afterwards!
これからもずっと一緒にいてね！
Please stay together with me forever!
鮮やかなストーリー描いてゆくよ
Painting a vibrant story as we go on,
いつまでも君と手をつないで
holding your hand forever.
進む道の先に何が待っていても
No matter what awaits us ahead on our path,
怖くなんかないよ 笑顔でいよう
I'm not afraid at all, let's keep smiling.
響き合うメロディ 空に響かせて
Let our resonating melody echo through the sky.
未来へと続くこの道を歩こう
Let's walk this path leading to the future.
小さな一歩が 大きな奇跡に変わる
A small step turns into a great miracle.
どんなときも信じているよ
I believe in you no matter what.
駆け抜けた日々が 私の宝物
The days we ran through are my treasure.
これからもよろしくね 大好きな君へ
Thank you for everything, to my dearest you.
どこまでも広がる 青空の下で
Under the endlessly spreading blue sky,
手と手を取り合って 進んでいこう
hand in hand, let's keep moving forward.
夢見た未来が 今、始まるよ
The future we dreamed of is starting right now.
最高の物語を一緒に紡ごう
Let's weave the ultimate story together!
せーのっ
One, two!
でもそんなんじゃだめ
But that's just no good,
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, still not enough,
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart keeps evolving more and more!
言葉にすれば消えちゃいそうな関係なら
If our bond would vanish if put into words,
言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた 恐れてた
I thought of erasing words and feared it.
だけどあれ? なんかちがうかも
But wait? Maybe something's different.
千里の道も一歩から!
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a step!
石のようにかたいそんな意志で
With a resolve as hard as stone,
ちりも積もれば山となでしこ!?
Dust piles up into a mountain of grace!?
「し」抜きで いや「死ぬ」気で!
Without dropping dead, no, with all my life!
ふわるふわる ふわるふわる
Floating softly, floating softly,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
When you call my name,
それだけで宙へ浮く
That alone makes me float to the skies.
ふわるふわる ふわるふわる
Floating softly, floating softly,
あなたが笑っている
When you are smiling,
それだけで笑顔になる
That alone turns me to a smile.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God,